govroles.com 2010-06-15

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**GovRoles.com Privacy Overview**

GovRoles.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We want to provide a safe, secure user experience. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private, and is used only for the purposes as set forth herein. The following reflects our commitment to you.

**Information About All GovRoles.com Visitors**

We gather information about all of our users collectively, such as what areas users visit most frequently and what services users access the most. We only use such information in the aggregate and not on an individual basis. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can develop a better overall website for our users. This information may be shared with our partners, but only in the aggregate, so that they too may develop a better overall career website for you, as well.

**Information About You Specifically**

In some instances, such as when you sign up to use a service, enter into a contest, or purchase a product, we may need more specific information about you, such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, etc. We may use that information to make you aware of additional products and services which may be of interest to you, or to contact you regarding site changes. We may also ask you for other information, such as feedback regarding the site, the types of jobs you are interested in, and so on in an effort to make this the best career site available for our users.

**General Information Disclosure**

We do not disclose information about your individual visits to GovRoles.com, or personal information that you provide, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, etc., to any outside parties, except as set forth below.

    1\. To companies and individuals we employ to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, or processing credit card payments. These companies and individuals will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any other third party.

    2\. We disclose information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary.  
**  
Resumes**

Since GovRoles.com is a career site, we give you the option of putting your resume in our database, to be searched by prospective employers / recruiters or responding to individual ads with your resume. If you allow your resume to be searchable, then all recruiters who access our resume database product will have access to your resume. We use our best efforts to grant access to this database only to recruiters, hiring managers, headhunters, and human resource professionals. However, we are not responsible if some other third party, such as someone posing as the aforementioned evades security measures and gains access to the database, and, subsequently, your resume. You may remove your resume from our searchable database at any time. However, recruiters who have access to the database may have retained a copy of your resume and saved it in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of resumes in these instances.

**Policy Changes**

In the event of a policy change at GovRoles.com, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about GovRoles.com privacy policy, please feel free to contact us. Thank you for choosing GovRoles.com. We'll continue working to make this your favorite website to manage your career.
